http://www.axialis.com/axialis/privacy-policy.html

Volume Licensing
What is Axialis Lifetime License?
Blog
Special Offers!
Internet user privacy and confidentiality is important to Axialis. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our
practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
Information Collection and Use
Axialis is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Unless the user provides it voluntarily, Axialis does not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors of the website. Some pages permit visitors to request additional information. Visitors are able to e-mail messages to Axialis that will contain the user's
name and e-mail address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message.
Axialis uses the information visitors provide about themselves to fulfil those visitors' requests. E-mail addresses are used to answer messages received only.
Information Collected During Purchase
When you place an order on-line with us, we use a third-party e-commerce service provided by SWREG. You can access their privacy policies at SWREG privacy statement.
We do not keep credit card information as part of your product registration.
We keep information about purchasers in our database (name, email address, mailing address, phone...) to fulfil purchaser request only (lost program, keys...). Axialis may use purchaser information to send free upgrades, information about lifetime license or special rebates. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties.
Information Collected During Registration
During registration of products on-line (after purchase), users specify limited information about them. Axialis may use this information to provide with notices of new information that may be of use or interest to users. This may include newsletters, tutorials, website update notices, or notification on the availability of new products, and product updates. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others. Occasionally a user may be asked to provide a statement, provide a reference, authorize a quote or testimonial, or participate in a press release or case study.
No user is obligated to provide any details about the product or it's use. No statements will be taken or used without prior written consent.
Log Files
We use IP addresses and domain names to analyse trends and administer the site. IP addresses and domain names are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Axialis is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Axialis website.
Security
Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, Axialis cannot promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. Axialis does, however, utilize industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using firewalls and security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information. In some areas of our website, we require a user ID and password for you to access certain information. Axialis will not disclose such passwords to third parties; however, you are responsible for maintaining the privacy and security of your password.
Notification of Changes
Axialis reserves the right to change our privacy policy from time to time. If Axialis decides to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect from them, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose this information to third parties. If at any point Axialis decides that we wish to use personally identifiable information collected from our users in a manner that differs from that stated at the time this information was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice whether or not to consent to our using their personal information in accordance with our updated privacy policy.
Products
IconGenerator
IconWorkshop
Screensaver Producer
CursorWorkshop
Fluent Pro 2018 icons
Flat Pro 2017 icons
Line Design icons
Microsoft, Windows, Windows XP, Windows Vista are registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation
Adobe, Flash, Photoshop, Illustrator are registered trademarks of Adobe System Incorporated
